Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 1, Folder: 21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Classification and Pay Plan Distribution List, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    By J.S. Frazer. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Public Employees' Retirement System, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Group Health Care & Life Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Class Specification, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Group Health Care & Life Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Personnel Rules, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Supervisor's Guide: Labor Contract Administration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Job Listings, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Performance Evaluation Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Rater's Guide to Performance Evaluation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Box: 2, Folder: 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Now That You Are a Member, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Box: 2, Folder: 3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Box: 2, Folder: 4 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: General Information on Food Processing, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: General Information on Brewing Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Box: 2, Folder: 5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Application of Employment, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Clerical and Technical Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Rater's Manual for Work Performance Rating, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Production Supervisory Work Performance Rating, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Supervisory and Administrative Work Performance Rating, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Non-Exempt Office Employees Work Performance Rating, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Manual for the Classification of Non-Exempt Salaried Jobs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Box: 2, Folder: 6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Communications, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Wage and Salary Administration Materials, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Box: 2, Folder: 7 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Salary Continuation Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Job Classifications, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Cooperative Group Insurance for Employees at Buffalo Plant, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Your Future in Allied Chemical, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Employees Educational Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Effective Community Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Public Relations in Plant Emergencies, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Energy, Chemicals, Fibers and Fabricated Products, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: A.M.: Daily for Employees of Morris Township Center, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Gus Merkel/June Mosher. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 8 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labor's State in NY's 2nd Largest Manufacturing Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Box: 2, Folder: 9 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Chronological History of the 1947 West Allis Strike, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Would you Sign Your Name to under this?: Anti-Communist Pamphlet, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Next Five Years: Pamphlet on Contract between Allis Chambers and Local 248 UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Joint Statement before the House of Representatives: Comt. On Education and Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Works Council, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Company Letters to Employees: Strike 1946-1947, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Walter Geist. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Vacation-With-Pay-Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Resume of Pertinent Phases of AC Labor History Depicting Destructive Effect of Communist Control of a Labor Organization, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Bargaining in Good Faith Against Overwhelming Odds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: History of Bargaining Units, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: It's Not as easy as that!: Anti-Communist Pamphlet, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: The First Hundred Years, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: An Explanation of Federal and WI State Income Tax Laws, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Industrial Teaching; Education Bulletin No. 9, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Bound List of Materials, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Chronology of Collective Bargaining and Negotiation Activities, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Box: 2, Folder: 10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Daily Labor Report; Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan: Negotiated Between CIO's UAW and Allis Chalmers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Mutual Aid Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Retirement Guide, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining Agreement between AC Gadsen Works and Local 487 of UAW, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Collective Bargaining Agreement between AC and The Pattern Makers League, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: 1950-55 Agreement between AC and The Pattern Makers League, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Questionnaire on Industrial Relations Activities for Allis Chalmers Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Employees' Mutual Benefit Assoc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Statement of Policy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Memorandum on Hours of Work in Defense Industries-Allis Chalmers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Letter to Stockholders: Strike Timeline, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Max Babb. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Memorandum on Industrial Relations Activities for Allis Chalmers Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Educational Dept. Questionnaire, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Letter to J. Douglas Brown Regarding Princeton Request, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By E.J. Beddard. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Apprentice Indenture, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Letter to Stockholders: Strike Situation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Training Supervisors for More Efficient Plant Operation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By R.G. Greiner. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Letter to Employees About the Strike Situation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Newsweek Reprint: Red Hands at Allis, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Application for Trade Apprenticeship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Newspaper Articles regarding Strike, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: WE of Allis Chalmers: Our Women Work for Victory; Vol. 2 No. 5, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Fired: 14 Centuries of Labor; Newsletter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Box: 2, Folder: 11 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Daily Labor Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Letter to Stockholders Regarding Strike, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Special Supl. To Daily Labor Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Newspaper Article: Auto Union Votes Peace, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Agreement between AC and Local 248, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: WE; Vol. 5 No. 11, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: WE; Vol. 5 No. 3, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: WE; Vol. 5 No. 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: WE; Scholarships, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: We; Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: We; Years of Expansion, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: We; Insurance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: We; Credit Union, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Agreement between AC and Local 248, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: The Open Door to Opportunity; Employee Training, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Company Organization of Manpower, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Lee Hill. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 12 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Graduate Training Program for Engineers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Graduate Training Program for Engineers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: War Policies and Practices Survey of the Milwaukee Area, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Retirement and Pension Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Apprentice Training Program at West Allis Works, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Apprentice Draftsmen's Safety Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Letter to Employees re. National Safety Council Award, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By W.C. Van Cleaf. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Letter Regarding Strike, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Harry Twomey. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Alcoholism Pamphlet, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Logarithms Education Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Apprentice Production Electricians' Safety Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Apprentice Pattern Maker's Safety Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Apprentice Welder's Safety Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Apprentice Machinist's and Tool Maker's Safety Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: Rat Control, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By J.M. Jensen. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Industrial Dermatitis, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: Bulletin on Methyl Chloride, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: Safe Practice Bulletin for Mixed Acid, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By W.F. Scholtz. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Safe Practice Bulletin for Cyanide Compounds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: Military Service Policy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 21: Apprentice Production Electricians' Safety Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 22: Safe Practice Bulletin for Nitric Acid, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: Safe Practice Bulletin for Sulfuric Acid, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 24: Safe Practice Bulletin for Trichloroethylene, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 25: Aluminum Dust, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 26: Toxicity of Some Chlorinated Solvents, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 27: Safe Practices for Handling of Acid or Alkali Cleaners, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 28: Safe Practices for Handling of Acids and Caustics, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 29: Safe Practice Bulletin for Ammonia, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 30: Safe Practice Bulletin for Methyl Chloride, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 31: Safe Practice Bulletin for Cyanide Compounds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 32: Methods of Sterilization of Protective Equipment at West Allis Works, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 33: Sand Blast Helmet Procedures, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 34: Safe Practice Bulletin for Hydrofluoric Acid, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 35: Procedure for the Inspection and Testing of Portable Ladders, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 36: Safe Practice Bulletin for Isopropyl Alcohol, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 37: Prospectus of Apprenticeship System, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 38: Graduate Student Contract, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 39: Safe Practice Bulletin for Hydrochloric Acid, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 40: Apprenticeship Contract, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 41: Cooperative Student Contract, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Box: 2, Folder: 13 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Benefits for Salaried People-Springfield Works, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Maintaining Discipline, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Mutual Aid Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Retirement and Pension Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Retirement and Pension Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Field Service Safety Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Railroad Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Safety Always, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: College Tuition Refund Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Graduate Training and Education Services, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: The Next Five Years: Pamphlet on Contract between Allis Chambers and Local 248 UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Are you interestedBrochure, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Company Information Sheet, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Company Information Sheet, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Medical Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Products/Divisions and Subsidiaries, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 19: Plan of Basic Medical Benefits, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 20: Award for Merit, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 21: Making a name for yourself, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 22: Training Program for Managers and Supervisors, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 23: Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 24: Guide to Relocating Employees and Their Families, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 25: Benefits Program for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 26: Products/Divisions and Subsidiaries, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 27: The Firm and Its Products, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 28: Careers in Technical Marketing, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 29: The Firm and Its Products, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 30: Guide to Products and Services, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Box: 2, Folder: 14 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Agreement with Local 248 of UAW, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Agreement with Local 248 of UAW, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Agreement with Local 248 of UAW, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Agreement with Local 248 of UAW, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: We work in a great tradition, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Union Calendar No.714; House of Representatives: Report No. 1508, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Charles Kersten, Thomas Owens, John F. Kennedy. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: National War Labor Board Directive Order, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: You and the Returning Veteran, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Allis-Chalmers. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Maintenance and Construction Manual, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Railroad Manual, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Bulletin of Illinois Institute of Technology: Graduate Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Time Cards/Badges, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Statement of Policy under The National Industrial Recovery Act, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Employee Record, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Employee Record, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Employee Record, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Things Every Employee Should Know, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Vacation-With-Pay-Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Agreement with Local 248 of UAW, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Maintaining Discipline, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: The Supervisor's Guide for the Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: So you have a grievance to handle, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: It's Never Too Late to Learn, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: It's Never Too Late to Learn, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Works Council, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: A Word on the Discipline Control Board, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: The Problem Drinker in Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Management Aspects of Industrial Alcoholism, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Henry A. Mielcarek. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: We're Glad You're Back, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Constitution and By-Laws of the AC Mutual Aid Society, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Constitution and By-Laws of the AC Mutual Aid Society, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Industrial Training, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Your Future in the Foundry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Constitution and By-Laws of the AC Mutual Aid Society, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: On Military Leave, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Rules, Regulations and Instructions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The Door to Opportunity, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Crane Operating and Hitching, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Agreement with Local 119 of United Farm Equipment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Contract Proposal to Local 248 to Settle 1946 Strike, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Rules, Regulations and Instructions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Grinding Practices, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Women: Safe at Work, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Constitution and By-Laws of the AC Mutual Aid Society, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Rules, Regulations and Instructions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Box: 3, Folder: 3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Recreation Guide, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Employees' Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Safety Always, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Constitution and By-Laws of the AC Mutual Aid Society, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Mutual Aid Handbook, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Constitution and By-Laws of the AC Mutual Aid Society, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: The Apprentice System, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Field Service Safety Manual, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Constitution and By-Laws of the AC Mutual Aid Society, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Retirement and Pension Plan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Retirement and Pension Plan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Box: 3, Folder: 4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: It's Not as easy as that!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Bargaining in Good Faith Against Overwhelming Odds, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Supporting Documents I-III; V-XXIII with Statement of AC in Negotiations with Local 248, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Comparative Study of 1942 Demands of Local 248, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Box: 3, Folder: 5 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: It's Never Too Late to Learn, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Here's Help: Job Selection, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Apprentice Training Program at West Allis Works, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Box: 3, Folder: 6 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: College Tuition Refund Plan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Graduate Training Program Materials Kit, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Would you Sign Your Name to under this?: Anti-Communist Pamphlet, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Box: 3, Folder: 7 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Alcoholic Program: Results to Date, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The Problem Drinker in Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Introduction to Electronics; Education Bulletin No. 11, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Industrial Teaching; Education Bulletin No. 9, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: This is It: AC Clubs, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: A Report re. the Electrical Equipment Antitrust Cases, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Fractions and Decimals; Education Bulletin No. 6, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Practice Plates for Drafting Apprentices-Simple Detail; Education Bulleting No. 13, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Practice Plates for Drafting Apprentices-Advanced Detail; Education Bulleting No. 14, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Where do we go from here?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Box: 3, Folder: 8 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Job Analysis Guide, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Statement of AC in Negotiations with Local 248, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Joint Statement of AC Before House of Reps. Comt. On Education and Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Supervisory Handbook, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Box: 3, Folder: 9 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Industrial Teaching; Education Bulletin No. 9, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Blueprint Reading; Education Bulletin No. 7, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Rules and Practices for the Application of Electrical Insulation Coil Taping; Education Bulletin No. 4, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Slide Rule; Education Bulletin No. 3, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Shop Sketching; Education Bulletin No. 2, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Box: 4, Folder: 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: American Can Company Industrial Relations Manual; Vol 4: 4.20.5-4.34.24.11, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Box: 4, Folder: 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: American Can Company Industrial Relations Manual; Vol 4: 4.36.09.01-4.59.64B.15, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Box: 4, Folder: 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: American Can Company Industrial Relations Manual; Vol 4: 4.58.63.01-4.62.63B.11, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Box: 4, Folder: 4 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Your Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Progress Through Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    By William F. May. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Alternative Work Schedules, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Student Loan Program, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    By Sal J. Giudice. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Tuition Refund Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Managers Guide Exempt Performance and Development Review, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Creative Products: Recruitment Flyer, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Benefits Program, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Matching Grants to Higher Education, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Box: 4, Folder: 5 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employees' Manual, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Box: 4, Folder: 6 (Box 4, Folder 6)